INFO:



Name: Dmytro Hoi Phone: 0666756463

E-mail: me@dmytrohoi.com

LinkedIn: dmytrohoi
Site: dmytrohoi.com

SUMMARY:

I have been programming in Python for over two years. At the same time, I used Ubuntu for over a year, and Arch Linux (as a personal OS) for more than six months. I worked on the following projects: Telegram bots for parsing sites, for connecting to the server via the REST API and for creating reminders; several small personal projects on Django; script for faster creation and deployment of a personal site; contribution to some projects on GitHub. [more on dmytrohoi.com/blog/projects]

My work experience contains: the American company is in the position of QA and Script Developer, where I used SQL, RegExp, WebQL and JS to parse sites (and some business tools); the International outsource company as a Python/Ruby QA Automation Engineer, where I used Appium, Python, pytest, ADB and many other tools for create Test Framework for Android Pie device. I have the basic skills of a programming engineer: HTTP stack, HTML/CSS, SQL, RegExp, Bash/zsh, Git (a specific tools: Gerrit, git-flow). I understand: the principles of DRY/OOP/SOLID, REST API, design patterns in QA/SE and several BA tools (Jira, Jama). My additional programming languages is: Javascript, Pascal/Delphi, sh and Ruby. I am studying System Analysis, including machine learning.

SKILLS:

- Languages: primary Python/Go, secondary* JavaScript, Ruby, sh**, Pascal/Delphi
- Libraries: pytest, Appium, python-telegram-bot, SQLAlchemy, requests, bs4, tkinter
- Frameworks: Jupyter(+Lab), Django*, Flask*
- IDE/Code Editors: VSCode**, Atom, VIM*
- English-level: Intermediate
- OS: Ubuntu, Arch
- VCS: Git, SVN
- Tools: Jira, Trello, (other types of Kanban)
- Other: HTML/CSS, SQL, RegExp**, GitHub**, Virtual Environments/Docker

^{* -} in progress, small experience or was used once-twice in projects

^{** -} used every day and gaining experience

ADDITIONALS SKILLS:

- Algorithmic & Design thinking
- Initiative
- Public speaking skill
- Process automation loving
- Writing (<u>habr.com/users/dmytrohoi</u> | <u>dev.to/dmytrohoi</u> | <u>t.me/s/progsrc</u>)
- Photoshop, Office, Draw.io and else basics
- SMM, PR, Poems writing

PERSONAL PROJECTS:

- <u>Telegram Bots</u>
- Kiwi Tickets Parser (with GUI)
- Pelican Make Site script
- Misc Work Scripts (with GUI Eel)

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Company: National University of Radioelectronics

Position: Senior Assistant (06/2016 - 05/2017)

Info: Quality Assurance Department ISO 9001 using for internal quality assurance system

Company: Gwara Media

Position: Site Support Specialist (03/2018 - 06/2018)

Info: HTML, CSS, WordPress editing

Company: Microbilt

Position: Site Scraping Script Developer (07/2018 - ...)

Info: WebQL programming, using RegExp and Python for creating misc automation

scripts

EDUCATION:



<u>Kharkiv National University of</u> <u>Radioelectronics</u>

- Bachelor (2014 - 2018) Electronics - "Electronics devices and systems"

- Master (2018 - 2020) System Analysis - "Consolidated information"

DMYTRO HOI / Oct 2019 2/2

E-mail: dmytro.hoi@gmail.com | LinkedIn: dmytrohoi | Site: <a